Guide to the First Presbyterian Church (Cazenovia, N.Y.) records, 1799-1952.
First Presbyterian Church (Cazenovia, N.Y.) records, 1799-1952
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
First Presbyterian Church (Cazenovia, N.Y.) records, 1799-1952.
2060
First Presbyterian Church (Cazenovia, N.Y.)
1 cubic ft., 1 reel pos., 1 reel neg. microfilm.
Minutes, accounts, correspondence, lists, historical data, guestbook, receipts, checkbooks, treasurer's reports, and other records.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Session records; minutes; lists of marriages, baptisms, and members; minutes, accounts, and correspondence of women's organizations, including the Woman's Foreign Missionary Society and the Torrey Circle of Kings Daughters; historical data; guestbook; correspondence pertaining to early pastors, especially Joshua Leonard; receipts, checkbooks, and treasurer's reports; and other records of the Cazenovia First Presbyterian Church.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Session records; minutes; lists of marriages, baptisms, and members; minutes, accounts, and correspondence of women's organizations, including the Woman's Foreign Missionary Society and the Torrey Circle of Kings Daughters; historical data; guestbook; correspondence pertaining to early pastors, especially Joshua Leonard; receipts, checkbooks, and treasurer's reports; and other records of the Cazenovia First Presbyterian Church.
SUBJECTS
Names:
First Presbyterian Church (Cazenovia, N.Y.); Leonard, Joshua, 1769-1843.
Subjects:
Presbyterians.; Religion.; Women in the Presbyterian Church.
Places:
Cazenovia (N.Y.)
Form and Genre Terms:
Registers.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Minutes of the Session, 1887-1925 (Box 1)
- Membership list, including deaths, dismissals, excommunications, suspensions, marriages, 1850-1886 (Box 1)
- "An Address Presented to the Presbytery of Onondaga," Joshua Leonard (pamphlet), 1813 (Box 1)
- Guest register, 1943-1949 (Box 1)
- Minute book and financial record, 1846-1902 (Box 1)
- Account book, 1905-1944 (Box 1)
- Church Treasurer's Record, 1925-1929 (Box 1)
- Church Treasurer's Record, 1929-1932 (Box 1)
- Church Treasurer's Record, 1933-1938 (Box 1)
- Secretary Reports of the Torrey Mission Band, including minutes and constitution, 1881-1889 (Box 1)
- Accounts of the Torrey Circle of Kings' Daughters, 1897-1906 (Box 1)
- Torrey Circle Book, cash book, 1906-1908 (Box 1)
- Torrey Circle, minutes, 1910-1921 (Box 1)
- Torrey Circle of Kings' Daughters, bank book, 1919-1951 (Box 1)
- Torrey Circle, checkbook, 1945-1950 (Box 1)
- Torrey Circle, cancelled checks (envelope), 1949-1951 (Box 1)
- Torrey Circle of Kings' Daughters, bank book, 1952 (Box 1)
- Ladies Christian Association, treasurer's report, 1900-1912 (Box 1)
- Woman's Foreign Missionary Society, Secretary's book, 1915-1917 (Box 1)
- Cabinet of the Women's Circle, minutes, 1948-1951 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1897-1898 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 1)
- Torrey League, correspondence, 1890-1897 (Box 1)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, reports, and receipts, 1947-1952 (Box 1)
- "A Book of Church Records of the Presbyterian Church in the Town of Cazenovia, gathered and established May 19, Anno Domini 1799 by Joshua Leonard A.M., first Pastor of sd. Church" (microfilm; original volume returned to the church along with several other volumes in 1974), 1799-1846 (Box 1)
  Admission of members listed from beginning in 1799 in text.
  Lists of members: 1799-1813, begins on p. 170-176; 1813-1846, begins on p. 40-67. Names not in alphabetical order. The year or complete date of death of member is often given under Remarks.
  Lists of Baptisms: 1799-1813, pp. 160-163; 1814-1846, pp. 88-101.
  Lists of Marriages: 1799-1813, pp. 164-167.